krreddy.in 2014-05-28

# Privacy Policy | Krreddy.in

**Privacy Policy**

In the Privacy Policy of  “krreddy.in” we explain how we collect and use private information from customers when they interact with us. At krreddy.in, we value our customers and are committed to protecting your privacy, as well as safeguarding the information we receive and maintain about you. We do not sell information about you to others. We only share it as expressly allowed by law. Consequently, you do not need to notify us not to share information about you, because we have chosen to limit this for you. This Notice will help you understand what information we collect, how we use it, and the ways we maintain your privacy and the security of personal information about you.

**Use of cookies**

krreddy.in use cookies for the sole purpose of finding whether a customer has visited our site previously and whether he/she has set any preference already. Our cookies are not devised to retrieve any data from a hard drive and it could not obtain an e-mail address. More over, krreddy.in customers have the facility to change the browser setting any time they like so that they can either accept or reject all cookies or even notify the user when a cookie is sent.

**Usage of collected data**

We collect only the bare necessary personal information from our customers for the smooth running of the business. The data collected will be used only for the purpose for which it is collected. The personal information collected will not be shared with any third party.

**Customer’s responsibility**

It is the customer’s responsibility to contact the respective merchants and to get necessary details of the product which they intend to purchase, its quality, warranty, shipments etc. krreddy.in is not responsible for the above act. The discounts, coupons, bidding, competitions, survey etc offered by different merchants are made available to customers through this site.

**Links**

krreddy.in maintains links with many other Websites for business purposes. All Websites have their own Privacy practices and we have nothing to do with them. Again, with regard to the content in other websites also, we have no control or responsibility. Hence customers are cautioned to check the third party privacy policies before submitting personal data and committing yourself.

**How we use collected information**

krreddy.in may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
  * **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Please feel free to contact us for further clarification and for further details.**
